{
    "subject": "resource/Centerville,_Indiana",
    "predicate": "property/subdivisionName",
    "object": "resource/Indiana",
    "human_readable": "Centerville, Indiana is a subdivision of Indiana.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9635483026504517,
            "question": "To which state does Centerville, Indiana belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.960294783115387,
            "question": "Is Centerville, Indiana a part of a larger region?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9558455944061279,
            "question": "What state is Centerville, Indiana located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9538465142250061,
            "question": "In which geographical area is Centerville, Indiana situated?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9399940967559814,
            "question": "Can you provide the name of the state that contains Centerville, Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9277657270431519,
            "question": "Is Centerville, Indiana a city or a town?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9192001819610596,
            "question": "What type of entity is Centerville, Indiana classified as?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8883420825004578,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Centerville, Indiana and Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8759744167327881,
            "question": "What level of administrative division is Centerville, Indiana?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7249395847320557,
            "question": "What political entity governs Centerville, Indiana?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Centerville, Indiana is a subdivision of Indiana.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4434_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What level of administrative division is Centerville, Indiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4434_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the relationship between Centerville, Indiana and Indiana?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4434_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of entity is Centerville, Indiana classified as?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4434_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4434_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4434_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4434_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4434_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4434_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4434_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4434_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4434_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4434_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4434_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents do not provide any information to support that Centerville, Indiana is a subdivision of Indiana. Centerville is described as a town located within Wayne County in the state of Indiana, but it is not referred to as a subdivision."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "Centerville, Indiana is not a subdivision of Indiana but rather a town located within Wayne County, which itself is a county within the state of Indiana.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Centerville is a town located within Wayne County, Indiana, which means it is not a subdivision of the state itself but a part of the county.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}